<Peliculas>
<Pelicula_Spider-Man_3>
 <title>Spider-Man 3</title> <type>movie</tipe> <runtime>139 min</runtime> <genre>Action, Adventure</genre> <director>Sam Raimi</director> <writer>Sam Raimi (screenplay), Ivan Raimi (screenplay), Alvin Sargent (screenplay), Sam Raimi (screen story), Ivan Raimi (screen story), Stan Lee (Marvel comic book), Steve Ditko (Marvel comic book)</writer> <actors>Tobey Maguire, Kirsten Dunst, James Franco, Thomas Haden Church</actors> <awards>Nominated for 1 BAFTA Film Award. Another 3 wins & 31 nominations.</awards> <released>04 May 2007</released> <year>2007</year> <language>English, French</language> <metascore>59</metascore> <imdbRating>6.2</imdbRating> <plot>Peter Parker has finally managed to piece together the once-broken parts of his life, maintaining a balance between his relationship with Mary-Jane and his responsibility as Spider-Man. But more challenges arise for our young hero. Peter\'s old friend Harry Obsourne has set out for revenge against Peter; taking up the mantle of his late father\'s persona as The New Goblin, and Peter must also capture Uncle Ben\'s real killer, Flint Marko, who has been transformed into his toughest foe yet, the Sandman. All hope seems lost when suddenly Peter\'s suit turns jet-black and greatly amplifies his powers. But it also begins to greatly amplify the much darker qualities of Peter\'s personality that he begins to lose himself to. Peter has to reach deep inside himself to free the compassionate hero he used to be if he is to ever conquer the darkness within and face not only his greatest enemies, but also...himself.</plot> <poster>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BODUwMDc5Mzc5M15BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNDgzOTY0MQ@@._V1_SX300.jpg</poster>
 <puntajeUsuario>0</puntajeUsuario>
</Pelicula_Spider-Man_3>
<Pelicula_Dragon_Ball_Z>
 <title>Dragon Ball Z</title> <type>series</tipe> <runtime>24 min</runtime> <genre>Animation, Action, Adventure</genre> <director>N/A</director> <writer>N/A</writer> <actors>Doc Harris, Christopher Sabat, Sean Schemmel, Terry Klassen</actors> <awards>N/A</awards> <released>13 Sep 1996</released> <year>1996\xe2\x80\x932003</year> <language>Japanese, English</language> <metascore>N/A</metascore> <imdbRating>8.8</imdbRating> <plot>After learning that he is from another planet, a warrior named Goku and his friends are prompted to defend it from an onslaught of extraterrestrial enemies.</plot> <poster>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMTM1NTY1MTcxNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTcwNzE3MjMyMQ@@._V1._CR10,7,274,430_SX89_AL_.jpg_V1_SX300.jpg</poster>
 <puntajeUsuario>0</puntajeUsuario>
</Pelicula_Dragon_Ball_Z>
<Pelicula_LEGO_Batman:_The_Movie_-_DC_Super_Heroes_Unite>
 <title>LEGO Batman: The Movie - DC Super Heroes Unite</title> <type>movie</tipe> <runtime>71 min</runtime> <genre>Animation, Action, Adventure</genre> <director>Jon Burton</director> <writer>Jon Burton, David A. Goodman</writer> <actors>Clancy Brown, Troy Baker, Christopher Corey Smith, Charlie Schlatter</actors> <awards>N/A</awards> <released>21 May 2013</released> <year>2013</year> <language>English</language> <metascore>N/A</metascore> <imdbRating>6.6</imdbRating> <plot>Presidential Candidate Lex Luthor teams up with the joker to destroy Batman and Superman while becoming president. Will the duo of Batman and Superman win or will they be taken down and destroyed with the rest of the justice league. Based On The Thrilling Video Game Lego Batman 2 DC super heroes.</plot> <poster>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BMjE4MTU5MDk5OF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNDQ1NzA2MDE@._V1_SX300.jpg</poster>
 <puntajeUsuario>0</puntajeUsuario>
</Pelicula_LEGO_Batman:_The_Movie_-_DC_Super_Heroes_Unite>
<Pelicula_Dracula>
 <title>Dracula</title> <type>movie</tipe> <runtime>85 min</runtime> <genre>Fantasy, Horror</genre> <director>Tod Browning</director> <writer>Bram Stoker (by), Hamilton Deane (from the play adapted by), John L. Balderston (from the play adapted by), Garrett Fort (play)</writer> <actors>Bela Lugosi, Helen Chandler, David Manners, Dwight Frye</actors> <awards>2 wins & 2 nominations.</awards> <released>14 Feb 1931</released> <year>1931</year> <language>English, Hungarian, Latin</language> <metascore>N/A</metascore> <imdbRating>7.6</imdbRating> <plot>After a harrowing ride through the Carpathian mountains in eastern Europe, Renfield enters castle Dracula to finalize the transferral of Carfax Abbey in London to Count Dracula, who is in actuality a vampire. Renfield is drugged by the eerily hypnotic count, and turned into one of his thralls, protecting him during his sea voyage to London. After sucking the blood and turning the young Lucy Weston into a vampire, Dracula turns his attention to her friend Mina Seward, daughter of Dr. Seward who then calls in a specialist, Dr. Van Helsing, to diagnose the sudden deterioration of Mina\'s health. Van Helsing, realizing that Dracula is indeed a vampire, tries to prepare Mina\'s fiance, John Harker, and Dr. Seward for what is to come and the measures that will have to be taken to prevent Mina from becoming one of the undead.</plot> <poster>http://ia.media-imdb.com/images/M/MV5BNTg5NjkxMjUxNF5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwNzk1NDc2MTE@._V1_SX300.jpg</poster>
 <puntajeUsuario>0</puntajeUsuario>
</Pelicula_Dracula>
